What comes to mind when you think of a museum?
想到博物馆时你头脑中会浮现什么？
Perhaps you picture an imposing building in a rather traditional design made of high-quality stone?
也许你会想象一座由优质石材建造、设计相当传统的宏伟建筑？
Perhaps you imagine one of the classic concepts, such as the museum of natural history, the museum of fine art, or the national museum - its exhibits displayed in a time-honoured style and falling in line with convention.
也许你会联想到一种经典概念，比如自然历史博物馆、美术博物馆或国家博物馆——其展品以历史悠久的风格陈列，遵循传统。
Some people might consider these customary institutions the best way to safeguard the future of typical educational topics.
有些人可能认为这些特有机构是保护典型教育主题未来的最佳方式。
A museum of antique breadboards, they may say, does not constitute an orthodox or legitimate exhibition.
他们可能会说，古董面包板博物馆并不构成正统或正当的展览。
But according to the Museums Association, a museum is defined as a place enabling "…people to explore collections for inspiration, learning and enjoyment."
但根据博物馆协会的定义，博物馆是一个让“……人们探索藏品以获得灵感、学习和享受”的地方。
And so of the 2500 estimated museums in the UK, a few are bound to be considered a little unconventional, eccentric or even niche.
因此，在大约英国的2500家博物馆中，有一些必然被认为有点非传统、古怪甚至小众。
No matter how atypical your interest, there's a museum for you!
无论你的兴趣多么不典型，都有适合你的博物馆！
What about Neil Cole's Adventures in Science Fiction?
尼尔・科尔的“科幻冒险”博物馆如何？
This quirky museum of classic science fiction was opened by founder Neil Cole.
这家古怪的经典科幻博物馆由创始人尼尔・科尔开设。
Visitors to this Allendale attraction in Northumberland can see items ranging from props used in the BBC series Dr Who to part of Thor's costume from the Avengers movie.
参观诺森伯兰郡阿连代尔这个景点的游客可以看到从BBC剧集《神秘博士》使用的道具到《复仇者联盟》电影中雷神的部分服装等物品。
"Science fiction has become more mainstream so I thought people might want to see this," says Mr Cole.
科尔先生说：“科幻已经变得更主流，所以我认为人们可能想看看这个。”
If clocks are more to your taste, why not visit the Cuckooland Museum?
如果时钟更符合你的口味，为什么不参观布谷鸟钟博物馆呢？
Set up by brothers Roman and Maz Piekarski, this Cheshire collection of over 600 cuckoo clocks is considered to be the largest of its kind in the world – and all from the Black Forest region in Germany.
这家位于柴郡的博物馆由罗曼和马兹・皮耶卡尔斯基兄弟建立，收藏了600多座布谷鸟钟，被认为是世界上同类收藏中最大的——且展品全部来自德国黑森林地区。
Finally, you could visit the Viktor Wynd Museum of Curiosities in London.
最后，你可以参观伦敦的维克多・温德奇物博物馆。
This offbeat, alternative institution bucks the trend of educating visitors through written explanations alongside its curios.
这家另类、非传统的机构打破了通过奇物旁的文字说明来教育游客的趋势。
Instead, it displays all of its kooky treasures, which include dodo bones, shrunken heads and a collection of McDonald's Happy Meal toys, with no explanation at all. These are just a few examples.
相反，它展示所有古怪的藏品，包括渡渡鸟骨骼、缩小的头颅和一系列麦当劳开心乐园餐玩具，完全没有任何说明。
There are many more wonderful institutions out there that march to the beat of their own drum.
这些只是几个例子。
All you have to do is go and find them!
还有许多很棒的机构独树一帜，你只需要去发现它们！